

Muhammad Baber

Date of birth: 16/08/1989

Nationality: Pakistani

Gender: Male

CONTACT

b/3 house no railway socity model colony , karachi, Pakistan (Home)

muhammad.babar16@gmail. com

(+92) 3012655175

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/muhammad-baber

03012655175 (Whatsapp)

ABOUT ME

I am a flexible and experienced insurance administrator with excellent time management skills. I am a good communicator with proven inter personal skills and am used to working in a team whilst also being capable of using own initiative. I am skilled In dealing with problems in a resourceful manner and negotiating to achieve beneficial agreement. I am always enthusiastic to learn and undertake new challenges.

WORK EXPERIENCE

14/01/2014 - 31/12/2022 karachi, Pakistan

Home furnishings shop sale person

curtain & fabric interior my responsibility

- · customer relation
- · goods communicate
- · as sale person
- team work
- time management
- supply work processes complete

29/01/2013 - 30/12/2013 karachi, Pakistan

Car engineering technician mechanical department

my workshop responsibility

- brake service
- oil change
- car inspection
- Tyre pressure check
- · wheel balancing
- car service

15/12/2012 - 30/12/2012 karachi, Pakistan

internshipe automobile amantech

technician training only fifteen day

- usage tools
- · two port lift
- · power tools
- job card read
- car inspection
- · how can work in workshop

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

2011 - 2012 karachi, Pakistan

Technician Certificate Moter Vehicale amantech institute city & guilds

2007 - 2010 karachi, Pakistan

Auto & Diesel Technology (DAE THREE YEAR) Sind Board st.patrick's technical institute

2006 - 2007 karachi, Pakistan

♦ Matric Computer Science maria model secondary school

LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): urdu
OTHER LANGUAGE(S): English

DIGITAL SKILLS

Microsoft Office | Microsoft Excel | Social Media | Facebook | Microsoft Powerpoint | Microsoft Word | Google Drive | Video Conferencing (Zoom, Teams, Skype, Webex) - Advanced | Installing and operation of Microsoft XP, Windows 7,8 & 10 MS-Office | linkine | Internet, Email | Software Installation

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Communication and interpersonal skills

good communication skill

- Able to work individually as part of co-located team
- Strong problem solving and analytical skill
- Hard working and self motivated
- Quick learner

Hobbies and interests

reading watching & listing

- cricket
- newspaper
- music
- movie

Reference

can be furnished upon request